{
    "subject": "Danielle_Spencer__Australian_singer_",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Russell_Crowe",
    "human_readable": "Danielle Spencer, an Australian singer, is married to Russell Crowe.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8652191758155823,
            "question": "Who is married to Danielle Spencer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.860660195350647,
            "question": "Who is Russell Crowe known for being married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7039279937744141,
            "question": "What country are both Danielle Spencer and Russell Crowe from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6935640573501587,
            "question": "Is Danielle Spencer a musician?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6317607760429382,
            "question": "Where is Danielle Spencer from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6016533374786377,
            "question": "Is Russell Crowe an Australian actor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6011656522750854,
            "question": "Name an Australian singer."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5104545950889587,
            "question": "What nationality is Danielle Spencer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4352685213088989,
            "question": "What profession does Danielle Spencer have?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.25045913457870483,
            "question": "Are there any famous couples who are Australian?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Danielle Spencer, an Australian singer, is married to Russell Crowe.",
            "html": "yago_8040_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What profession does Danielle Spencer have?",
            "html": "yago_8040_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What nationality is Danielle Spencer?",
            "html": "yago_8040_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name an Australian singer.",
            "html": "yago_8040_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8040_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8040_107.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8040_120.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8040_140.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8040_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8040_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8040_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8040_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8040_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8040_80.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Danielle Spencer, an Australian singer, is married to Russell Crowe.\" The details in multiple files indicate their marriage and Spencer's background as a singer."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Several news articles state that Russell Crowe and Danielle Spencer have separated after nine years of marriage.",
            "category": 0
        }
    }
}